<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<NewsFeed>
  <News Date="8/10/2018 8:50:10 AM" Imp="True" Display="ALL">iPayment has changed their name to PaySafe.</News>
  <News Date="7/1/2018 8:48:54 AM" Imp="True" Display="ALL">All new service installs, not completed by the sales rep, will be billed 1 hourly minimum for installation and training of our products and services including PCI compliance at either the standard $40/hr. or premium $50/hr., depending on the level of experience of the installer, and will be billed at minimum 1hr increments thereafter as necessary.  The sales rep. can offer this services for free, at cost or mark up the to the customer for their standard commission split over cost.  The cost of standard has been increased from $35-40/hr. and premium from $40-50/hr. to better reflect our actual labor costs and the sell rate of standard has been increased from $75-80/hr.</News>
  <News Date="3/1/2018 10:33:24 AM" Imp="True" Display="ALL">Sage Payment Solutions has changed their name to Paya.</News>
  <News Date="1/2/2018 2:16:12 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Starting 1/1/2018 all referral bonuses will be charged back for accounts not remaining active for at least 12 months instead of the previous 6 months.</News>
  <News Date="9/12/2017 4:42:04 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">We no longer offer any form of leasing for hardware including through our previous vendors Duvera or Northern leasing.  We do have financing and rental options for Revel systems only.</News>
  <News Date="1/1/2017 8:31:45 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">As an additional incentive, we will now begin paying referral fees for re sellers per our affiliate schedule as we do for employees, affiliates and agents paid at the standard percentages of 30% and 60%.  Any partners paid at a higher percentage will no longer be eligible for payment of referral fees.</News>
  <News Date="7/1/2016 1:44:58 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Offer free Sage One accounting software with all new Sage merchant accounts!  See our web site https://firstaffiliates.com/Affiliatewiz/SageAccountingSoftware.aspx for more information.  Make sure you add the new sales opportunity Sage One so it is fulfilled and setup properly.  There is no cost or profit to the sales partner, this is simply a great up sales tool that merchants have been asking for when not needing a more sophisticated product such as Quickbooks. </News>
  <News Date="4/1/2016 9:02:38 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Revel will no longer allow us to display retail pricing of its bundles to the public so we have changed the pricing of each on our store http://store.ecenow.com/tablet to (call for pricing) but you can see the retail pricing of each bundle in the item list and calculate promotion discount (Limited time 20% off with 18 month contract) from there.</News>
  <News Date="1/1/2016 9:47:10 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Due to the decreased revenue potential of the following services we have reduced the referral fees as follows:  Payment gateways from $50 to $25 and merchant account add on services PIN debit and EBT from $25 to $0 for all fundings starting in 2016. See the commission schedule here https://www.firstaffiliates.com/Affiliatewiz/commissions.aspx for a complete list.</News>
  <News Date="10/16/2015 12:04:03 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">You can now upload Excel files through our online application and portal.  All agents who want a completed rate comparison reviewed will have to create an online application and upload the comparison and statement for review.  All rates in the application and should  match the comparison before we begin the review.</News>
  <News Date="6/1/2015 3:32:15 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Starting June 1st, all new Ingenico and Verifone terminals require the addition of a sales opportunity in the online application for Download-Terminal since TASQ will now perform them for $25.  Payment Technology is changing so rapidly that stocking inventory no longer makes sense.  This will provide better service to your customers with faster deployment, reducing out of stock wait time, ensuring they receive the latest version of hardware and software and eliminating the expiration of warranties which begin the day we bring the hardware in to our inventory. We will continue to download any remaining terminals we have in inventory, new software and payment gateways and perform reprograms of existing customer hardware, software and payment gateways for free.  </News>
  <News Date="4/17/2015 7:50:58 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Today we posted the new Sage application which includes AmEx OptBlue.  Now all of our processors are set up with OptBlue so you will now be able to price merchants AmEx as you wish for all but those few merchants that don't qualify.  Rates will default to the same as Credit if you don't specify otherwise.  Please see the Non Bancard FAQ's and AmEx section of Documents and Logins for more information on the process.</News>
  <News Date="8/19/2014 10:06:49 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">As of August first our new address is 2321 Rosecrans Ave. Suite 4270, El Segundo, CA  90245.  All phone and fax numbers remain the same.</News>
  <News Date="2/28/2013 5:01:47 PM" Imp="True" Display="Agents">We now pay you referal fees on accounts that you board with us- $100 per merchant account, $50 for additional services like the payment gateways and $25 for add-on services like the debit service. They are paid upfront even before you start making any residuals on it!</News>
  <News Date="2/28/2013 5:00:47 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">So we can pay upfront referral fees on every account, we are lowering the commissions from 90% to 80% and herby amending your agreement with us.</News>
  <News Date="2/1/2013 11:36:24 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">You may now upload your logo for display in your mirrored web site and online applicaiton with us through your profile!</News>
  <News Date="1/1/2013 11:34:17 AM" Imp="True" Display="ALL">Receive up to an $300 bonus for every sale in 2014 and 2015!  This promotion applies to the first new sale per customer and is paid out based on the same criteria as our affilaite program.</News>
  <News Date="10/11/2013 4:30:40 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Attention Agents! We are having a general training at our office Thursday and Friday February 20th and 21st 2014 at 8:00am. Please bring any questions you may have. The last hour will be devoted to our Act for Web training for those agents that want to work out of our office or take new lead calls.  You must RSVP with Monika Shivapuram.</News>
  <News Date="12/31/2011 4:59:31 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Attention Partners! We are pleased to announce that our residual reporting system has been upgraded and should work normal going forward.  Thanks for your patience as we added new features and reporting for new vendors.</News>
  <News Date="1/1/2013 12:06:03 PM" Imp="True" Display="ALL">Get an additional $100 for every funding in 2014-2015!
Pick your bonus/Set your target and notify us by the 1st business day of every month. It could be 3, 4, 5 or as many fundings as you choose. The bonus will be $300, $400, $500, etc. For example, your target bonus could be "5 fundings for $500." The logic is - Higher the Target, Higher the Bonus!</News>
  <News Date="9/24/2010 9:50:59 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Effective October 1st 2010, iPayment, Inc. will increase fees slightly in order to keep pace with changes that will be implemented by the associations.  
As always, it is important to review any new interchange pricing.  Ensure you are including these increases on merchant accounts boarded during the month of September 2010 and after. Please visit the card association websites for full interchange details.
 Visa:    http://usa.visa.com/merchants/operations/interchange_rates.html
MC:      http://www.mastercard.com/us/merchant/acceptance/interchange_rates.html
Visa/MC/Disc Acquiring Rates
5 basis points (0.05%) on Mid-Qualified
10 basis points (0.10%) on Non-Qualified
Discover:     
International Service Fee – A fee of 0.55% will be applied to transactions that are processed at a US Merchant location on a Foreign Issued card.  This fee is not applicable to JCB and China Union Pay.
Data Usage Fee – A fee of $0.0185 per transaction fee will apply to all settled Discover transactions.
Dues &amp; Assessments (November 2010):  Current Dues and Assessments fee of 0.0925% will increase to 0.10% as of October 2010.
PCI Compliance Fee (if merchant has not filled out the online PCI Questionnaire/SAQ):
Monthly Non Compliance Fee                           $30.00/month

Deadline for Monthly Non-Action Fee:  As a reminder, new merchants will have 90 days from the date they establish their merchant account to complete the process.  Merchants have a deadline each month to complete the PCI process in order to avoid being charged the monthly non-action fee.  This date is the 24th of each month.  A merchant must complete the entire PCI process (including scanning if required) by the 24th of any given month to avoid the $30 monthly non-action fee.  Once the process in confirmed and completed, they must repeat this process annually and repeat required scanning quarterly.  
Merchants are being notified of the above rate changes on their September 2010 statements.</News>
  <News Date="9/3/2010 5:33:41 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Effective October 1st 2010, Intuit Payment Solutions will increase fees slightly in order to keep pace with changes that will be implemented by the associations. These increases will exclude merchants approved after May 1, 2010.  
 The resulting increase will include: 
 1)      15 basis points (0.15%) increase for "non-qualified" sales for existing and future QuickBooks Merchant Service (QBMS) merchants. The new "non-qualified" rate will be 3.69%. 
2)      $2.00 monthly fee increase for existing and future Intuit Point of Sales Merchant Service customers.
3)      $3.00 monthly fee increase for existing merchants using a terminal.
4)       Some PIN-based Debit Networks are increasing their rates. Please visit http://www.innovativemerchant.com/support/debit_fee_sched.php to review all debit network pricing changes.</News>
  <News Date="6/29/2010 11:12:57 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">After analysis of the previously announced July 2010 Visa Dues &amp; Assessments increase, iPayment will be increasing merchants affective for July 2010 processing as outlined below.
Merchants are being notified of these changes on their June 2010 statements.
Discount Rates:
3 basis points (0.03%) on Mid-Qualified and Non-Qualified
Interchange and Dues Pass Thru Accounts:
Visa Dues will be increased to the new cost of 0.11%.</News>
  <News Date="4/4/2010 8:57:56 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Cost of Goods has now been renamed Item List since it encompases services and other items such as bonuses, shipping options, returned check fees, etc.  We have added images and links for associated brochures to help you better understand and sell each item.  All Items in the Item List can have opportunities created for them in the Edit Opportunities section of each online application.  
Agents can now buy direct at 10% over our cost and without having to associate the item with a customer.</News>
  <News Date="4/4/2010 8:50:02 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Payroll is the first new product we have added to our line of services in a number of years.  Please see the section on our web site for more information.  Customers can sign up through the online application or by calling our sales queue.  You will be compensated just as you are with any other add on service.</News>
  <News Date="3/1/2010 10:13:26 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">We are pleased to announce the launch of our new web site with a new color scheme, improved navigation, lead management, shopping cart offering all of our products at 20% above cost and an online application which will allow signing of all of our services 24 hours per day.  You have a mirror of our actual web site available from your home page which you can use to market as your own.  You will also have the ability to turn on or off lead notification, product pricing, add your own URL and other features to come through your profile.</News>
  <News Date="10/2/2008 9:10:27 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Starting October 1, 2008, non-qualified rates for all IMS merchants will be increased by 12bps (0.10%) and iPayment, Inc. merchants will be increased 10bps (0.10%).   Merchants were notified of the increase on their August Statements.  Any new merchants signed on in the month of September, 2008 with IMS will be given a 3 month grace period and will not be affected until January 1, 2009.</News>
  <News Date="3/17/2008 11:46:42 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Visa USA and MasterCard International have announced an interchange rate increase effective for April 2008.  In consideration of this rate modification, we are simply passing on our cost to you, our valued partner.  
As always, it is important to review the new interchange pricing and make sure you are including it on any new accounts you are quoting.  Please make sure to account for new pricing on Merchants you board during the month of March 2008. 
Visa USA Interchange Increase:
-  Signature Preferred – Card Not Present            +10 basis points       2.30% + $0.10
-  Signature Preferred – Electronic                      +10 basis points       2.30% + $0.10

MasterCard International Increase:

          

MasterCard has added new Merit 1 interchange categories for Insurance and Real Estate.  These new levels will be pointed to Non-Qual for all merchants.
-  Merit 1 Insurance (Consumer, Enhanced and World)     1.43% + $0.05
-  Merit 1 Insurance World Elite                                   2.20% + $0.10
-  Merit 1 Real Estate (Consumer, Enhanced and World)   1.10% + $0.00
-  Merit 1 Real Estate World Elite                                 2.20% + $0.10
-  Merit 1 Real Estate Debit                                        1.10% + $0.00.
After analysis of this increase, iPayment, Inc. will be raising all merchants by 10 basis points (0.10%) on their Mid-Qualified and Non-Qualified rate effective for April processing.  In conjunction with the Visa/MasterCard rate increase, the pin debit networks have also announced an interchange rate increase effective for April 2008.
After analysis of this increase, iPayment, Inc. will be raising all merchant’s pin based debit transaction fee by $0.10, to be capped at $0.45.  So if a merchant is already paying $0.40 per transaction, they will only go up to $0.45, if a merchant is paying more than $0.45 per transaction, they will be lowered down to $0.45.

 

In addition, merchants paying less than 0.75% or no additional basis points on pin debit, will be raised to 0.75% (this is in addition to their per transaction fee).   This fee will also be capped, at 0.75%.  So if a merchant is currently priced higher than 0.75%, the fee will be lowered.

 

The monthly debit access fee is not affected by this increase and will remain the same.

 

New Agent Cost:                0.75% + $0.35.


Merchants will be notified of these increases on their February statements.
</News>
  <News Date="12/1/2007 4:33:14 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">As of today, Discover will now be set up as part of the Visa/MC merchant number.  The applications have changed to reflect the new proceedure.  Merchants will be billed the same rates you offer for Visa and MC.  Agents &amp; Resellers will now begin to earn revenue based on your costs above Discover Interchange rather than the previous one time set &amp; activation bonuses.  Discover Voice authorizations will be handled through the respective platform rather than Discover.  In time, all previous merchants will also be converted to this new structure.</News>
  <News Date="11/22/2007 2:30:18 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Happy Thanksgiving!  We've moved so please make a note of our new address, phone &amp; fax numbers in the contact us tab.  We will be open normal business hours 11/23.   However we will just be getting situated in our new home with a new phone system so please be patient over the next few weeks.</News>
  <News Date="9/10/2007 9:30:20 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">With the upcoming October Rate Increase by Visa/MC, please be aware of what is changing and how we’re handling this for iPayment merchants.
MasterCard Interchange Updates
-         Corp Data Rate 2      
        Current Rate:                                        2.05% + $0.00
        New Rate as of October 2007:                   2.32% + $0.10 (adding 27 basis points and $0.10)
-         Corp Standard 
        Current Rate:                                        2.70% + $0.10
        New Rate as of October 2007:                   2.95% + $0.10 (adding 25 basis points)
-         Corp Face/Face
        Current Rate:                                        2.05% + $0.00
        New Rate as of October 2007:                   2.32% + $0.10 (adding 27 basis points and $0.10)
Visa Interchange Updates:
-         No Changes Announced
 Merchant Account Changes
-         All merchants - non-qualified will be going up 5 basis points as of their October 2007 statements.
-         Anywhere we have the above changing interchange levels pointed will be adjusted as follows:
        If currently going to Mid-Qualified , moving interchange to Non-Qualified
        If currently going to Qualified, moving interchange to Mid-Qualified</News>
  <News Date="7/30/2007 4:51:26 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">As you may already be aware, effective August 1st, 2007, we will be converting our sponsor bank from JP Morgan Chase to Wells Fargo for the iPayment app only.  This change will have the following effects:
1. After August 10, 2007, we will not accept any Chase documentation for processing.  If a Chase app is received, you may be asked to go back to the merchant to sign the proper paperwork.
2. The app. is a little longer due to new PCI and Wells Fargo requirements.  It will also incorporate additional services such as EBT (which is a separate addendum with Chase), Debit (which is a separate addendum with Chase), and leasing (we don't have an agreement with First Data leasing but may in the future &amp; will be happy to help you with a direct relationship if you prefer in order to offer one app. for almost all services). 
3. All references to Chase on your marketing materials, business cards, website and the like, need to be updated to read “Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., Walnut Creek, CA” vs. “JP Morgan Chase, Hicksville, NY.
4. New Merchant Applications and Agreements have been posted to the Documents and Logins page of the Partner Portal for those agents that require hard copies of the application.  The online application should be updated by the 1st.  
We appreciate your cooperation and value your business. Please take the time to review the app. so that you become familiar with all required fields.   Please call Susanne Lopez if you have any questions, concerns or need a training of the new application.</News>
  <News Date="5/21/2007 4:21:59 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Please welcome the addition of Vina Prince to our staff. She has been in the industry for over 11 years and will make a great addition to our company. She will be your contact for all products and services fulfillment, installation and customer service.  Susanne Lopez will no longer be taking care of these duties and will now be your contact for all of the following:   sales support, agent training, review of all new applications and orders prior to submission to underwriting, the prospective vendor and through approval.  Their contact information can be found in the "Contact Us" tab.</News>
  <News Date="4/12/2007 10:17:05 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">We now offer direct deposit.  To sign up, click yes on the -Do you want to sign up for Direct Deposit?- button within your Edit Profile link.  Fill in your banking information.  Then print, complete and e-mail or fax the Authorization Agreement with a void check to Charmaine Cruz.</News>
  <News Date="4/12/2007 10:06:12 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Visa and MasterCard have announced that they will be restructuring some of their processing rates.  Due to the restructuring, IMS will be making changes to fees effective May 1 for all accounts approved previous to that date.  We are excited to announce a reduction in the qualified rate by 4 basis points for those merchants that are set up with a swiped rate. This is due to the fact that we will be moving some rewards cards from qualified to mid-qualified and others from mid-qualified to non-qualified. However, in order to keep pace with the associations, we will need to increase the non-qualified rates. The increase will include an additional 13 basis points for non-qualified sales. For example, a $100 sale would result in an additional $.13 for a “non-qualified” sale.   For Ipayment merchants set up before March 2007 their non-qualified rates will include and additional 15 basis points.  All merchants at the above processors will be notified via message on their March Statements.</News>
  <News Date="1/2/2007 10:15:18 AM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Happy New Year!  As an additional incentive to sell value added services in addition to our core merchant account services, as of 1/1/2007 all payment gateway, ctcart.com hosting and/or shopping cart services, online debit, check services other than Authorize.net ACH which counts as a payment gateway, Gift and Loyalty, and merchant advance funding will count as 1/2 of a merchant account sale towards quotas, bonuses and goals provided they are sold at the minimum or above and funded during the current month.</News>
  <News Date="10/29/2006 7:53:57 PM" Imp="False" Display="ALL">Due to the fact that Authorize.net residuals have always been paid one month earlier than all other residuals, September Authorize.net residuals will be paid in November rather than October to get them on the same schedule.</News>
</NewsFeed>