<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<Pages>
  <Page>    
    <Title>Credit Card Processing, Merchant Services, Payment Processing</Title>
    <PageName>default.aspx</PageName>    
    <description>Start accepting credit cards within the next 24 hours with the lowest rate with a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1999.</description>
    <keywords>
      Services, Merchant, Solutions, card, merchant services, merchant account, merchant account service, apply merchant account, POS accounting, secure, QuickBooks, Intuit local service, Intuit Primer reseller, new merchant account, loyalty card services, merchant cash advance,	gift loyalty card, accounting integration, Payment gateway, accept credit card payments, check services, payroll services, Cash advance
    </keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>    
    <Title>E-Commerce Solutions</Title>
    <PageName>ecomsolutions.aspx</PageName>    
    <description>Provides a complete secure transaction processing payment gateway system, a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>virtual terminal, affiliate program, electronic checks, AIM, SIM, terminal, authorization, ach, merchant account, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, amex, American express, authorize, advanced integration, agent program, join, earn money, merchant account, authorize.net, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>    
    <Title>Electronic Check Service </Title>    
    <PageName>echeck.aspx</PageName>    
    <description>Payment service that allows online and traditional merchants to accept and process electronic check payments.</description>
    <keywords>echeck, electronic check, electronic check service, ach, ssl, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, amex, American express, authorize, advanced integration, agent program, join, earn money, merchant account, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Check Services</Title>
    <PageName>CheckServices.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Payment services that allow online and traditional merchants to accept and process electronic checks from consumer and corporate bank accounts safely and securely regardless of whether the business is retail, mail/phone order or internet-based.</description>
    <keywords>Check 21+, Point of sale, pos, checks, check guarantee, online debit, debit, echeck, electronic check, electronic check service, ach, ssl, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, amex, American express, authorize, advanced integration, agent program, join, earn money, merchant account, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>    
    <Title>Virtual Terminal</Title>
    <PageName>virtualterminal.aspx</PageName>    
    <description>Manual entry of electronic check and credit card transactions.</description>
    <keywords>virtual terminal, overview, virtual terminal configuration, test account, vpos, virtual point of service, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize, advanced integration, agent program, join, earn money, merchant account, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>    
    <Title>Web Links</Title>
    <PageName>weblink.aspx</PageName>    
    <description>Automate credit card transactions directly from your Website by integrating to the authorize.net Payment Gateway.</description>
    <keywords>advanced integration, simple integration, authorize.net, payment gateway, automate, web link, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize, advanced integration, agent program, join, earn money, merchant account, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>    
    <Title>Info Center</Title>    
    <PageName>infocenter.aspx</PageName>    
    <description>Understand how e-commerce works.</description>
    <keywords>understand e commerce, how it works, faq, payment gateway, automate, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, merchant account, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>    
    <Title>Free E-Consultation</Title>
    <PageName>consult.aspx</PageName>    
    <description>Understand E-Commerce. Fill out the free consultation form to get more information.</description>
    <keywords>free consultation, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>    
    <Title>Request an Application</Title>
    <PageName>apply.aspx</PageName>    
    <description>Understand E-Commerce. Fill out the free application to get more information.</description>
    <keywords>ecommerce, free application, shopping cart, apply,  understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Products and Services</Title>
    <PageName>prodservices.aspx</PageName>    
    <description>Lists products and services offered, equipment, software, payment gateways.</description>
    <keywords>us merchant services, international, merchant services, echeck, electronic check, check gurarantee, gift card, loyalty, ebt, merchant funding, merchant master, equipment, software, payment gateways, magtek, nurit, shopping cart, apply,  understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>    
    <Title>Equipment</Title>
    <PageName>equipment.aspx</PageName>    
    <description>Provides a list of equipment, mobile applications, accessories, software, payment gateways.</description>
    <keywords>equipment, mobile charge, nurit, magtek, verifone, 8000, omni, bartizan, flatbed, portable, 4200, 5500, hypercom s9, hypercom t7, micrimage, check reader, magtek usb, nurit 3010, 8320, 2085, printer, merchant master, pccharge, pc charge, imprinter slips, swivel, mobile applications, accessories, payment gateways, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, products, services, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment, POS solutions, POS, QuickBooks, Intuit, Point-of-Sale, hypercom, Cash register plus, POS hardware, POS software</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Secure Payment Gateways</Title>
    <PageName>gateways.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Lists payment gateways offered for credit card authorization.</description>
    <keywords>authorize.net, ach, automated clearing house, echeck, electronic checks, plug n pay, innovative, optimal, world pay, verisign, trust commerce, e-xact, credit card terminal, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Merchant Master Software</Title>
    <PageName>merchmaster.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about merchant master, pccharge express and pro.</description>
    <keywords>merchant master, pccharge, pc charge, mmpro, ebt, point of sale, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>US Merchant Services</Title>
    <PageName>merchant.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about US merchant services.</description>
    <keywords>us merchant services, merchant services, discount rate, transaction fee, merchant account basics, monthly fee, avs, visa, mastercard, american express, bank, banking, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>International Merchant Services</Title>
    <PageName>international.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about international merchant services.</description>
    <keywords>international merchant services, international account, worldpay, worldpay gateway, gateway, laser, solo, visa electron, diners, jcb, switch, merchant services, features, benefits, online sales, bank, banking, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Gift and Loyalty Card Services</Title>
    <PageName>gift.aspx</PageName>
    <description>We offer Gift and Loyalty Cards that can be used for all kinds of businesses: restaurants, retail and department stores, services, business to business, and gift cards can also be used for internet and online purchases, and mail order/telephone order purchases.</description>
    <keywords>Gift and Loyalty card Programs, Loyalty card Programs, Gift and Loyalty Cards, Restaurants loyalty cards, Customer, rewards and bonuses</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Understanding E-Commerce</Title>
    <PageName>understanding.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Understanding e commerce exchange basics including merchant account basics and other services.</description>
    <keywords>understanding ecommerce, shopping cart, basics, bank, banking, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Frequently Asked Questions</Title>
    <PageName>faqs.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Answers to frequently asked questions about e-commerce, merchant accounts and payment gateway. We are a leading provider of e-commerce solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>frequently asked questions,ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, pci compliance, PCI, PCI PED</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>About US</Title>
    <PageName>aboutus.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Information about our company and the services we provide. We are a leading provider of e-commerce solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>fast setup, quick approval, easy installation, website integration, low startup investment, 95% approval rate,ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, iPayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Sage Accounting Software</Title>
    <PageName>sageaccountingsoftware.aspx</PageName>
    <description>We offer a range of Sage 50 Accounting software earlier known as Sage Peachtree provides solution for every business type, whether you are starting new business in your basement or have multiple locations and dozens of employees.</description>
    <keywords>Sage 50 Accounting Software, Peachtree, Sage 50, Accounting Software , Accounting solutions, Sage 50 Quantum, top accounting software, compare accounting software, sage payroll software, small business accounting software</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Accounting Software</Title>
    <PageName>accountingsoftware.aspx</PageName>
    <description>We offer integrated, automated accounting system choose from Intuit QuickBooks accounting software or Sage Accounting Software.</description>
    <keywords>Financial Accounting Software, accounting software, Intuit QuickBooks Accounting Software, Sage 50 Accounting Software, automated accounting software, Accept credit card payments, integrated payroll service</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>QuickBooks Accounting Software.aspx</Title>
    <PageName>QuickBooksAccountingSoftware.aspx</PageName>
    <description>We offer Intuit’s QuickBooks accounting software which is the #1 rated and best selling small business financial software. This user-friendly system comes in 3 flavors-Pro, Premier and Enterprise Solutions</description>
    <keywords>QuickBooks Accounting Software, Intuit’s QuickBooks, small business financial software, QuickBooks, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, accounting and financial software, QuickBooks Financial Software Comparison</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Unacceptable Countries and Businesses list</Title>
    <PageName>unacceptablecountriesbusinesses.aspx</PageName>
    <description>List of Unacceptable countries and businesses. We are a leading provider of e-commerce solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, iPayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Available Gift and Loyalty Card Packages/Services</Title>
    <PageName>gift2.aspx</PageName>
    <description>We offer wide selection of choices for Gift card and Loyalty card packages. Merchants can choose from ready made PredDesigned Packages, Logo Design Packages, Custom Design Packages. We offer all packages at affordable price.</description>
    <keywords>Gift and Loyalty Card Packages, PreDesigned Card template, Holiday gift cards, Gift and Loyalty Cards</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>How eCommerce Works</Title>
    <PageName>howitworks.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Detail information on how and when your customer's funds reach your business bank account. We are a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Shopping Carts</Title>
    <PageName>shopcart.aspx</PageName>
    <description>A list of shopping carts integrated our payment gateways (includes both recommended and supported shopping carts). We are a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>shopping cart, prostores, ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Affiliates</Title>
    <PageName>affiliate.aspx</PageName>
    <description>E-Commerce Exchange Partner Program. Earn Commissions upto $300 per sale. We are a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>partner, affiliate, commissions, residuals, ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Agents</Title>
    <PageName>agent.aspx</PageName>
    <description>E-Commerce Exchange Partner Program. Earn Commissions upto $300 per sale. We are a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>partner, agent, commissions, residuals, ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Resellers</Title>
    <PageName>reseller.aspx</PageName>
    <description>E-Commerce Exchange Partner Program. Earn Commissions upto $300 per sale. We are a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>partner, reseller, bank affiliate, commissions, residuals, ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Partner Programs</Title>
    <PageName>partnermain.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Partner Programs. Earn Commissions upto $300 per sale. We are a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>partner, agent, affiliate, reseller, bank affiliate, premier partners, commissions, residuals, ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Premier Partners</Title>
    <PageName>partners.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Premier Partners. Earn Commissions upto $300 per sale. We are a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>partner, agent, affiliate, reseller, bank affiliate, premier partners, commissions, residuals, ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Merchant Account, Payment Gateway, Non-Bankcard Logins</Title>
    <PageName>merchantsplash.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Merchant Login Page. We are a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>partner, referral, commissions, residuals, ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Email Us</Title>
    <PageName>email.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Email Us Page. We are a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>partner, referral, commissions, residuals, ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Contact Us </Title>
    <PageName>contactus.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Contact Us Page. We are a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>partner, referral, commissions, residuals, ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Privacy Policy</Title>
    <PageName>privacypolicy.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Privacy Policy Page. We are a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>privacy policy, partner, referral, commissions, residuals, ecommerce, faq, leasing, address verification service, avs, pos, online application, jcb, amex, diners, discover,worldpay, ipayment, payment gateway, merchant account, what is merchant account, shopping cart, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Financial/Accounting and Point of Sale Software</Title>
    <PageName>software.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about financial/accounting software and POS software, QuickBooks Simple Start, QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, QuickBooks Point of Sale, Intuit Cash Register Plus, QuickBooks for Mac, merchant master, pccharge express and pro, a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>QuickBooks Simple Start, QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, QuickBooks Point of Sale, Intuit Cash Register Plus, QuickBooks for Mac, merchant master, pccharge, pc charge, mmpro, ebt, point of sale, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>QuickBooks Software</Title>
    <PageName>quickbookscomparison.aspx</PageName>
    <description>QuickBooks 2012 Financial Software Comparison.</description>
    <keywords>QuickBooks Financial Software Comparison, QuickBooks for Mac, QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions</Title>
    <PageName>QBEnterpriseSolutions.aspx</PageName>
    <description>We provide QuickBooks Enterprise Designed for businesses with more complex needs, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions offer all the benefits and features in QuickBooks Premier</description>
    <keywords>QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, QuickBooks Enterprise, QuickBooks, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks product, financial software, comparison of all the QuickBooks financial software.</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>GoPayment by Intuit</Title>
    <PageName>gopayment.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about Intuit GoPayment - a mobile phone based payment terminal by a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>Intuit GoPayment, QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, ebt, point of sale, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Mobile Payments</Title>
    <PageName>MobilePayments.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about Mobile Payemnts - mobile phone based payment terminal by a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>Intuit GoPayment, ROAMpay, ROAM data, Mobile Payments, QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, ebt, point of sale, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Wireless Services</Title>
    <PageName>Wireless.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about Wireless - Credit cards payments On-the-Go by a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>Wireless Services, Wireless Terminals, Intuit GoPayment, ROAMpay, ROAM data, Mobile Payments, QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, ebt, point of sale, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>ROAMpay</Title>
    <PageName>ROAMpay.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about ROAMpay service - Credit cards payments On-the-Go by a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>Wireless Services, Wireless Terminals, Intuit GoPayment, ROAMpay, ROAM data, Mobile Payments, QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, ebt, point of sale, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Laptop Payments</Title>
    <PageName>Laptop.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about Laptop processing - Credit cards payments on laptops by a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>Laptop processing, laptop payments, Wireless Services, Wireless Terminals, Intuit GoPayment, ROAMpay, ROAM data, Mobile Payments, QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, ebt, point of sale, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Wireless Terminals</Title>
    <PageName>WirelessTerminals.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about Wireless Terminals - Credit cards payments using Wireless Terminals by a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>Laptop processing, laptop payments, Wireless Services, Wireless Terminals, Intuit GoPayment, ROAMpay, ROAM data, Mobile Payments, QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, ebt, point of sale, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Field Service Management by Intuit</Title>
    <PageName>fieldservicemgmtes.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about Intuit Field Service Management by a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>Intuit Intuit Field Service Management, QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, ebt, point of sale, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Point of Sale Software Solutions</Title>
    <PageName>possolutions.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about POS Software, QuickBooks Point of Sale Basic, Pro, Multi-store, Intuit Cash Register Plus, QuickBooks for Mac, merchant master, pccharge express and pro by a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>QuickBooks Point of Sale Basic, Pro, Multi-store, Intuit Cash Register Plus, QuickBooks for Mac, merchant master, pccharge, pc charge, mmpro, ebt, point of sale, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>Accounting Integration</Title>
    <PageName>accountingintegration.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides solutions that integrate with accounting software QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, merchant master, pccharge express and pro by a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>QuickBooks Pro, QuickBooks Premier, QuickBooks Enterprise Solutions, merchant master, pccharge, pc charge, mmpro, ebt, point of sale, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>SSL Certificates from Comodo</Title>
    <PageName>ssl.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides options for SSL certificates needed when processing credit card data by a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>SSL, PCI Compliance, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
  <Page>
    <Title>PCI Compliance with Comodo HackerGuardian</Title>
    <PageName>pci.aspx</PageName>
    <description>Provides information about PCI Compliance and how to achieve compliant status by a leading provider of payment solutions for small business since 1989.</description>
    <keywords>SSL, PCI Compliance, payment server, check verification, check guarantee, CVV2, avs, discover, amex, gift card, understand e commerce, merchant account, payment gateway, credit card transactions, features, benefits, sale, products, services, earnings, e-commerce, ecommerce, affiliate program, merchant accounts, e commerce, credit card processing, accept credit cards online, agents, accept, affordable, about us, affiliate, accounts, application, approval, divcover, amex, American express, authorize.net, agent program, join, earn money, ims, ipayment</keywords>
    <COPYRIGHT>E-Commerce Exchange</COPYRIGHT>
  </Page>
</Pages>
